Mss.530.1.Ar2
American Philosophical Society
- I. Papers
  - Second volume of minutes of the Kapitsa Club, October 1933 - March 1958; 50.0 p.; Kapitsa, P. L., (Petr Leonidovich), 1894-1984 (Reel 38, Reel-frame 3)
    Bohr Collection, Copenhagen, Denmark. Letters to Niels Bohr, 12 letters, 1933-1946
    Rutherford Collection, Cavendish Laboratory, Cambridge, England. Letters to Ernest Rutherford, 2 letters, 1925-1933.
  - Letters to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 1942-1951; 4.0 Item(s) 4 letters (32 pages); Karreman, George, 1920-1997 (Reel 12, Reel-frame 12)
  - Letter to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 1950; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kastner, Robert (Reel 12, Reel-frame 12)
  - Letters to Walther Gerlach, 2 November 1921 - 20 October 1924; 4.0 Item(s) 4 letters (4 pages); Kaufmann, Walter, 1871-1947 (Reel 19, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letters to Alfred Landé, 6 April 1919 - 14 January 1922; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (5 pages); Kaufmann, Walter, 1871-1947 (Reel 4, Reel-frame 17)
  - Letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 4 November 1905; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (4 pages); Kaufmann, Walter, 1871-1947 (Reel 31, Reel-frame 11)
    Bohr Collection, Copenhagen, Denmark. Letter to Niels Bohr, 1934.
    Einstein Collection, Princeton, New Jersey. Correspondence with Albert Einstein, 2 letters, 1906-1947.
  - Letter to Niels Bohr, 10 May 1918; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kayser, H., (Heinrich), 1853-1940 (Reel BSC 4, Reel-frame 1)
    Related Archival Materials note
    Erinnerungen aus meinem Leben, 1936. An autobiography of Kayser. B.K18.
    Bohr Collection, Copenhagen, Denmark. Letter to Niels Bohr, 1923.
    Royal Society Library, London, England. 1 letter, 1912.
    Deutsche Staatsbibliothek, Berlin, Germany. Material at present held at the Westdeutschen Bibliothek, Marburg/Lahn, Germany. About 1200 letters on spectroscopy from Kayser's correspondence. (Darmstaedter Collection).
    American Institute of Physics, New York, New York. Letters to Robert Williams Wood, 2 letters, 1903-1906.
  - Letter to Edwin C. Kemble, 1935; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kean, C. H. (Reel 54, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letters to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 1937-1943; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (4 pages); Keesing, A. (Reel 10, Reel-frame 5, Reel 12, Reel-frame 12)
  - Letter to Niels Bohr, 31 January 1916; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Keesom, W. H., (Willem Hendrik), 1876-1956 (Reel BSC 4, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letters to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 26 August 1924 - 4 January 1938; 5.0 Item(s) 5 letters (6 pages); Keesom, W. H., (Willem Hendrik), 1876-1956 (Reel 8, Reel-frame 7, Reel 10, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letters to Arnold Sommerfeld, 29 April 1913 - 1 December 1941; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (6 pages); Keesom, W. H., (Willem Hendrik), 1876-1956 (Reel 31, Reel-frame 11)
    Deutsche Staatsbibliothek, Berlin, Germany. Material at present held at the Westdeutschen Bibliothek, Marburg/Lahn, Germany. Letters to Max Iklé, 4 letters, 1909-1913. (Darmstaedter Collection, Fla 1913).
    Rijksmuseum voor de Geschiedenis der Natuurwetenschappen, Leiden, Netherlands. Letter to L. S. Ornstein, 1913; letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1913.
    Duke University Archives, Durham, North Carolina. Letters to Fritz London, 7 letters, 1930-1938.
  - Letter to Erwin Schrödinger, 27 May 1927; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kellner, Georg, b. 1905 (Reel 41, Reel-frame 8)
    Bohr Collection, Copenhagen, Denmark. Letters to Niels Bohr, 4 letters, 1930.
    Einstein Collection, Princeton, New Jersey. Correspondence with Albert Einstein, 2 letters, 1929.
  - Letters to Herbert Stanley Allen, 1937; 5.0 Item(s) 5 letters (5 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letters to Samuel King Allison, 1933-1934; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letters to American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1933-1936; 12.0 Item(s) 12 letters (12 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to American Association of Physics Teachers, 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letter to American Association of University Women, 1932; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letters to American Institute of Physics, 1933-1937; 4.0 Item(s) 4 letters (4 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letter to A. M. Baehr, 1931; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letter to John Barnes, 1927; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to Ernst Bartholome, 1935; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letters to James H. Bartlett, 1936-1937; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (3 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letters to R. P. Bell, 1937; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letters to Raymond T. Birge, 14 April 1924 - 18 November 1932; 43.0 Item(s) 43 letters; Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 50, Reel-frame 2-10)
  - Letter to George Birkhoff, 1933; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letter to Max Born, 26 May 1926; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to Boston Society for Psychic Research, 1931; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letters to David Gordon Bourgin, 29 September 1925 - 6 April 1928; 12.0 Item(s) 12 letters (27 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to Gregory Breit, 2 May 1935; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letter to Edgar Buckingham, 1933; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letter to G. Burk, 1936; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letter to R. Calkins, 1936; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letters to Walter F. Colby, 1 December 1923 - 4 June 1926; 5.0 Item(s) 5 letters (10 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letter to College Entrance Examination Board, 1931; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letters to K. T. Compton, 27 February 1926 - 9 April 1930; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (3 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letters to James Bryant Conant, 1933-1935; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (4 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letters to Edward Uhler Condon, 1 October 1934 - 24 April 1937; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (3 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letter to F. H. Crawford, 1936; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letter regarding W. E. Danforth, 1931; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letters to Karl K. Darrow, 1933; 4.0 Item(s) 4 letters (4 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letter to Charles Galton Darwin, 11 February 1925; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letter to Harvey N. Davis, 1933; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letter to David Mathias Dennison, 13 February 1928; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letters to Gerhard Heinrich Dieke, 29 September 1925 - 14 June 1926; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (5 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letters to J. L. Dunham, 1929-1930; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (4 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letters to Charles W. Edwards, 1933-1934; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (3 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letter to Albert Einstein, 15 October 1935; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letter to E. Ellery, 1936; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letters to C. H. Fay, 1936-1937; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (4 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letters regarding C. H. Fay, 1935-1937; 4.0 Item(s) 4 letters (4 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letters to Eugene Feenberg, May 1932 - 1937; 14.0 Item(s) 14 letters (24 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 8)
  - Letters to John Ambrose Fleming, 1936; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letters to R. H. Fowler, 22 October 1925 - 19 December 1933; 4.0 Item(s) 4 letters (4 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 9, Reel 51, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letter to W. H. Furry, 1934; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letters regarding W. H. Furry, 1932; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (6 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letter to G. N. Gaboury, 1932; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letter to Alan Stuart Galbraith, 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letter to R. C. Gibbs, 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letter to Stanford Goldman, 1935; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter regarding Stanford Goldman, 1935; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter regarding Gottschalk, 1934; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letters to Samuel Abraham Goudsmit, 29 January 1930 - 1937; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (3 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 9, Reel 64, Reel-frame 1-2)
  - Letters to Harvard University, Milton Fund, 1932-1936; 4.0 Item(s) 4 letters (6 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 10)
  - Letters regarding Monica Healea, 1932; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 10)
  - Letter regarding Malcolm H. Hebb, 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 10)
  - Letters to Mayo Dyer Hersey, 1926; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (5 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 8)
  - Letters to Edward Lee Hill, 6 February 1934 - 1937; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 10)
  - Letter to Hirschwaldsche Buchhandlung, 1933; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 10)
  - Letters regarding W. V. D. Hodge, 1933; 7.0 Item(s) 7 letters (10 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 10)
  - Letter to W. V. Houston, 4 January 1934; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 11)
  - Letter regarding J. B. Howard, 1936; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 11)
  - Letters to Llewellyn Griffith Hoxton, 1935; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (3 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 11)
  - Letters to John Charles Hubbard, 1928-1935; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (3 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 11, Reel 51, Reel-frame 8)
  - Letter to Friedrich Hund, 31 March 1926; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 8)
  - Letters to Hubert James, 1936; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (3 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 11)
  - Letter to C. K. Jen, 1933; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 11)
  - Letter to C. H. Kean, 1935; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letters to T. S. Kemble, 1932-1933; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (5 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letters to Julian Knause Knipp, 1936-1937; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (3 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letters regarding Julian Knause Knipp, 1936-1937; 6.0 Item(s) 6 letters (6 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 2 January 1925; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 8, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letters to Adolf Kratzer, 22 August 1925 - 1925; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (5 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letters to Arthur B. Lamb, 1924-1926; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (5 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letter to Alfred Landé, 30 November 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to Rudolph Langer, 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letters to Robert Bruce Lindsay, 10 June 1933 - 1936; 10.0 Item(s) 10 letters (10 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to Fritz London, 17 February 1930; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letters to F. W. Loomis, 17 February 1925 - 1937; 23.0 Item(s) 23 letters (32 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 2, Reel 51, Reel-frame 10)
  - Letter to Theodore Lyman, 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letters to James MacKaye, 1933; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (3 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letters to Henry Margenau, 1934-1935; 4.0 Item(s) 4 letters (14 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letter to J. H. S. McCarthy, 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letters to McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1933-1935; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (4 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letter to John Moffatt Mecklin, 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letters to Dayton Clarence Miller, 1933-1936; 7.0 Item(s) 7 letters (7 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letters to Marston Morse, 1932; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (10 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letters to Robert Sanderson Mulliken, 24 January 1928 - 12 November 1935; 8.0 Item(s) 8 letters (8 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 4, Reel 52, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter regarding H. Munsterburg, 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letters to Kenneth B. Murdock, 1933; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (3 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letters regarding National Academy of Sciences, 1931-1937; 10.0 Item(s) 10 letters (10 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letters to National Research Council, 1925-1926; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (5 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 52, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letters to O. Neugebauer, 1933-1934; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letter to M. S. Nichols, 1936; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letter to J. Noyd, 1935; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letter to Otto Oldenberg, 18 December 1935; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letters to Optical Society of America, 1935-1936; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letters to Leigh Page, 1925-1926; 4.0 Item(s) 4 letters (5 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 52, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letter to Eugene Fred Parker, 1935; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letters to R. A. Patterson, 1933-1937; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letter to Linus Pauling, 18 October 1932; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letters to George B. Pegram, 1936; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letters to C. E. Pettibone, 1935; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letter to A. S. Prebensen, 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letters to Richard David Present, 1935; 6.0 Item(s) 6 letters (6 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letter to W. F. Prince, 1931; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letter regarding I. I. Rabi, 24 October 1936; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letters to F. K. Richtmyer, 1930-1936; 5.0 Item(s) 5 letters (6 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 52, Reel-frame 6, Reel 54, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letter to Sir Robert Robertson, 1928; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 52, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letter to G. W. Robinson, 1926; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 52, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letters to J. E. Rosenthal, 1935-1937; 5.0 Item(s) 5 letters (6 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letters to Arthur Edward Ruark, 8 February 1935 - 23 December 1935; 11.0 Item(s) 11 letters (13 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letters to Frederick A. Saunders, 1936; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (7 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 8)
  - Letters to Willard L. Severinghaus, 1936; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (3 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 8)
  - Letter regarding W. V. Smith, 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 8)
  - Letters to Marshall Stone, 1933-1934; 6.0 Item(s) 6 letters (9 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 8)
  - Letters to W. F. G. Swann, 1924-1937; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (6 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 52, Reel-frame 8, Reel 54)
  - Letter to Carl F. Taeusch, 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letters to John T. Tate, 1935-1937; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (3 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letter to W. P. Thorn, 1931; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letters to Richard Chace Tolman, 29 April 1926 - 5 June 1926; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (3 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 52, Reel-frame 8)
  - Letters to George Tunell, 1932; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (4 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letters to Harold Clayton Urey, 11 December 1924 - 11 February 1936; 7.0 Item(s) 7 letters (9 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 52, Reel-frame 8, Reel 54, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letters to J. H. Van Vleck, 29 August 1924 - 1937; 12.0 Item(s) 12 letters (20 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 49, Reel-frame 8, Reel 54, Reel-frame 10)
  - Letters to D. S. Villars, 1928-1933; 4.0 Item(s) 4 letters (5 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 10, Reel 52)
  - Letters to John Von Neumann, 18 November 1935 - 14 December 1935; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letter to William W. Watson, 1927; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 52, Reel-frame 10)
  - Letters to Enos Eby Witmer, 1934; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 11)
  - Letter to Peter I. Wold, 18 April 1930; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 7)
    Letter concerns Victor Guillemin.
  - Letters to Robert Williams Wood, 24 December 1923 - 6 May 1929; 7.0 Item(s) 7 letters (9 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 52, Reel-frame 11)
  - Letter regarding R. T. Young, 1935; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 11)
  - Letters to Clarence Zener, 1934-1936; 6.0 Item(s) 6 letters (6 pages); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 11)
  - Letter regarding William A. Zisman, 1933; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 54, Reel-frame 11)
  - Drafts of paper, "The Bohr Theory and the Planck Radiation Formula", 1919-1920; 36.0 p.; Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 55, Reel-frame 1)
  - Lecture course on quantum theory, "Physics 16a," Harvard University, 1919-1920; 210.0 p.; Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 56, Reel-frame 1)
  - Colloquium talk, "The Sommerfeld Development of the Bohr Theory and its Confirmation by Paschen", 1920; 10.0 p.; Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 55, Reel-frame 2.2)
  - Colloquium talk, "Low Temperature Specific Heats, Band Spectra, and Molecular Structure", 1920; 8.0 p.; Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 55, Reel-frame 2.3)
  - Colloquium talk, "Spectroscopic Evidence for a Metastable Modification of the Helium Atom", 1920; 16.0 p.; Kemble, Edwin C., (Edwin Crawford), 1889-1984 (Reel 55, Reel-frame 2.4)